This is BUIDL Readiness Reviewer, a CROO developer tooling agent for hackathon submissions.
The problem is simple: builders can have working code but still miss required submission evidence.
The result is a structured ReviewReport that turns submission rules into clear next actions.
The public GitHub repository contains the README, license, source code, submission copy, and logo.
The local commands are pnpm build, pnpm pre-submit, and pnpm demo.
The output makes it obvious what is ready and what still needs evidence.
The service layer is separated so it can be wired into the CROO provider SDK callback.
The demo uses placeholders only. Real keys are never pasted into chat, code, screenshots, or the video.
The current video is honest: local demo ready, provider template prepared, live CAP evidence still pending.
BUIDL Readiness Reviewer helps CROO builders turn submission requirements into a clear, callable review.